<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pastiche of life</title>
    <description>Random inspirations.
</description>
    <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://karthiksblog.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 12:24:59 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 12:24:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am standing in front of the God. Last time I stood like this, i remember it was for clearing my classical physics theory. This time the subject is chemistry, which is totally missing between us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is so much fun. I am extremely boring. 
She is simple. I used to compound my sentences and my poor choice of words often put people into anaphylactic shocks. 
Everytime I want to know more about her, I end up talking too much about me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is smart. I once thought of calling her out. I asked her &amp;quot;shall we go out for coffee?&amp;quot;.
She immediately replied &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t like coffee&amp;quot;. 
In trying to be smart, I asked back &amp;quot;what else do you drink? Tea?&amp;quot; with a sort of smile of my own, expressing &amp;#39;well! you can&amp;#39;t escape&amp;#39;. 
She replied, &amp;quot;beer&amp;quot; . 
My eyes went out, &amp;quot;what?&amp;quot;. 
&amp;quot;I drink beer&amp;quot;. 
&amp;quot;Okay!&amp;quot;. 
&amp;quot; Problem? &amp;quot;. 
&amp;quot;No. Not at all!&amp;quot;
She is smart. Naturally smart!
&amp;quot;Look at her smartness man&amp;quot;, I whispered to myself, &amp;quot; or may be she really drinks beer? &amp;quot; &amp;quot;how do people drink that shit?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work together. She comes to me for suggestions and ideas. Her designs are generally too good. But she sucks at presentation man. Once the client replied with a burning mail on seeing her proposal. It was about an idea of ad about his energy drink product. She had prepared two slides on what happens before and after drinking his energy drink, and sent him the slides flipping their names between each other.
The whole team laughed at her the whole day. We lost that client with that mail. Well, she simply comes to me for suggestions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other than the fact of working together, nothing works out for me. Wherever I try to impress her, I do it in front in people. There is not a single day I get paid with anything more than embarrassment and laughter. But she smiles at me and says, &amp;quot;but, that was good one&amp;quot;. She taps over my shoulder. I do it in front of others, well to see her smile more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am standing in front of God. Because she has said a yes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jyostna came to me yesterday and in her tutty voice asked me &amp;quot; you know how beautiful a bike ride in ECR is?!&amp;quot;
I said, &amp;quot;no. I only own a car.&amp;quot;
She whispered, &amp;quot;.........do you want to know?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;What?&amp;quot; I said to myself, &amp;quot;Is she asking you to take her out?&amp;quot; My mind spoke more words to me, than I would usually do to her &amp;quot;Dude! Check your pulse.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Check whether this is real world.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Check whether she is real her.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Just smile and say yes.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Smile at her.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Just say yes.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Oh wait, is she gonna show you how beautiful the ride is? That means, she already knows?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;My bad, she goes on dates with guys regularly?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Well chuck it. Just say yes.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Its just going to be fine, say yes!&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Say yes.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Wait, is she going to ask for a drink? A beer?.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Are you going to drink too? That disgusting fowl smelling liquid?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Yuck!&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Forget things.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Just say yes.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Oh, from whom am I gonna borrow bike?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Just say yes. Say yes bro! It&amp;#39;s the day for which you have been waiting. Say yes. &amp;quot; &amp;quot;Y E S.&amp;quot; 
And all those thought speakings happened in 5 seconds. The 5 seconds i kept silent, may be for first time ever in life. Starring at her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Pick me up tomorrow at 3pm?&amp;quot; She whispered. 
&amp;quot;Yes sure!&amp;quot; Instantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today is the day! I shouldn&amp;#39;t blow it up wrongly. It&amp;#39;s 12pm. I am standing in front of God. And also waiting for Alan to bring his bike. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today is the day, my friends. Today is the day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 11:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-1.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
