<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pastiche of life</title>
    <description>Random inspirations.
</description>
    <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://karthiksblog.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 13:03:03 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 13:03:03 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 9</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Distances bring people closer! Mumbai isn&amp;#39;t far from Chennai, atleast not after so much technological and scientific advancements. But it is far enough to bring Jyotsna closer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is another part. Mumbai has Roshan. Roshan is more than a friend. He is a part of me. There is a part of me, who will be alive only when Roshan is along. We are partners in crime. Way back, our PJs used to kill people like a slow pharmaceutical drug. He works as a guitarist for a few bands in Mumbai! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When God gives so many good things at same time, he sets up a difficult task of managing them together. &amp;quot;Roshan shouldn&amp;#39;t know about Jyotsna.&amp;quot; Way back, I used to hit on many girls. I had so many love stories and then there was Roshan in every climax of it. When we were just 16 years old, he told me &amp;quot;Machaan, I am pretty sure its love! Age isn&amp;#39;t a barrier. Have you seen Titanic? Leo is also younger to Kate. But look at their chemistry! Go tell her&amp;quot;. That was first time, a girl ever slapped me. She was the girl next door, who was 2 years elder to me and who teaching me calculus privately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most deadly one I remember was during my UG days. August is deadly month for all boys carrying both friendship day and Raksha Bandhan each year. After being friendzoned on first week of august and bro-zoned on third week, Roshan had asked me to still give a card to Archana on her birthday, in last week of august. I had asked another friend of mine, Sameer, to buy a card for me, since he lived next to Archie&amp;#39;s. It&amp;#39;s yet another occasion where my friend&amp;#39;s laziness screwed my day. Sameer had brought a card, which had words written from a girl&amp;#39;s perspective. Roshan showered his evil words, &amp;quot;Sachin, this card has some purpose for its existence. I think there is still some way in which you can give it to her&amp;quot;. His philosophies tested my IQ and I did find a way to give her. I gift wrapped the card without signing it, with a text over it &amp;quot;happy birthday dear. This gift contains something which is for someone special in your life&amp;quot; thinking that she would undersign it and give it back to me someday. Two weeks later, in second week of September, Sameer got the same card on his birthday undersigned by Archana. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was too difficult for me to manage replying Jyotsna&amp;#39;s emails and also meeting Roshan every day. But I wanted to do both. One Saturday night, he was performing along with a Jazz band in a pub. He had invited me for the same. I saw some fake faces, trying to understand Jazz but still act like they are enjoying. I heard a lot of &amp;quot;Arey! Kya baat hai bhaai&amp;quot;. Those guys were brilliant. At the end, Roshan took over the mike and said, &amp;quot;this is for my friend Sachin.&amp;quot; They then performed Raja sir&amp;#39;s RumBumBum improvised in their own style. Later we ate. We are foodies. When we get together, we eat food like partners Sehwag and Gambhir used to score runs for India. It was getting late. I wanted to go back and reply Jyotsna. Roshan caught me straight. &amp;quot;Ponnaa?&amp;quot;. I was speechless for a moment and later Roshan heard everything about Jyotsna. In some random conversation, he asked me, &amp;quot; by the way, when is her birthday?&amp;quot;. I didn&amp;#39;t know her birthday. Shame on me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came back to room and wrote my letter. I told her about concert and asked her about her birth date. Next day, as soon as I woke up I checked my inbox. She had replied. I felt sick. &amp;quot;I didn&amp;#39;t screw up just any day of her. I have screwed up the plans on her birthday.&amp;quot; I realised. I felt bad. I couldn&amp;#39;t reply to her. Guilt made me sicker. I rushed to meet Roshan for breakfast. Talked to him. Felt a little better. And then, Roshan took it over. &amp;quot;I understand you guys are in good terms and you don&amp;#39;t want complications here. But why should she call you out on her birthday in first place?&amp;quot; That made me think. &amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s louuu my bwoyyy&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you seen tom and jerry? The episode where jerry used to hit on a girly mouse? Jerry used to have two parts of his mind personified as angel and devil who will be little Jerrys in green and Red flying over his head? Roshan is my red devil. &amp;quot;Feb 14 is here. Aren&amp;#39;t you planning anything machaa?&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like always, he made me plan a surprise. Yes, I am taking an off! Flying to Chennai for a day. Don&amp;#39;t tell her. Shhhhhh!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-9.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-9.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 8</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;May be it was too much coffee all of a sudden. He had to leave to Mumbai for a workshop. His face was literally down on the ground. &amp;quot;Aww you are so cute! Just go Sachin! Nothing is gonna happen in a month&amp;quot;. He then smiled. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had gone to send him off. &amp;quot; How are you going to be in touch?&amp;quot; I asked him. He looked at my eyes for a while. 
&amp;quot;I will write letters!&amp;quot; He said with a smile.
&amp;quot;Are you kidding?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;No I am not. Check your e-mail inbox. It would have an electronic letter each day. You could reply to that.&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;You are mad Sachin.&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Not as mad as these ones&amp;quot; he pointed at a family who were waiting in airport, the man and the lady were drowned in their mobile phone and their kid was playing angry birds in a Tab. 
A warm hug. And then I watched him leave. It was indeed heavy. No wonder people used to say, &amp;#39;airports are places which often see the true emotions&amp;#39;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His first mail after reaching Mumbai went like this, 
&amp;quot;Jyo! 
Reached mumbai! Journey was smooth. It&amp;#39;s raining here and city looks sexy in the rain :) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I checked-in, first thing I ordered was a coffee. I am typing this mail taking sips on my coffee here. The smell of caffeine is so intimate that I can feel your presence around. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Need to rest now. Long days are awaited.
Will miss you,
Sachin&amp;quot;
I asked mom to bring a coffee to my room. I prepared myself to write a reply. 
&amp;quot;Sachin,
Happy to hear from you. Don&amp;#39;t take too much rest. Go explore the sexy Mumbai. New place and new people are the ones which excites you always. Though Mumbai isn&amp;#39;t a new city for you, people would definitely be. Look for good Vada Pav chat spots. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish there are some rains here too. Month of January and Chennai is showing a shade of summer. The coffee smell completes the void though :)
Missing you already,
Jyotsna&amp;quot;
So the coffee times gradually shifted from office to home. But my parents are the best people. If my mom asks for the second coffee powder packet in middle of the month, my father won&amp;#39;t analyse if she is adding coffee powder in every dish she makes. My maid won&amp;#39;t count the number of used tumblers from my room, when she picks them up for cleaning. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next day I had to wait for his mail till late night. And then I received a mail with one pdf attachment. 
&amp;quot;Hi Jyo,
Sorry for making you wait. I read all 10 mails that you had sent in mean time. 
I felt writing was more organic than typing. It took a while for me to make the scanner at my hotel to work with my tab. 
PFA my letter for today :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till next time,
Sachin&amp;quot;
This guy is mad! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had an elaborate letter. His hand writing made me go crazy at times, &amp;quot;I should buy some cursive writing books to him&amp;quot;. But his writing was as open as his speech. His words were as emotional as the tone of his voice. I was missing him. There was some pain, but I was loving it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-8.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-8.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 7</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When magic happens, there is attention. People sleep until then, but become hyper active all of a sudden! More than the gravity I had over her, we both pulled people&amp;#39;s eyes over us. We can only pretend that we are different people with different coffee mugs each time. Factually, the more we pretended, the more obvious it became! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Managers are the most complicated human beings on earth. When we have just started our relationship over coffees, Manoj would have already named our kids in his imagination! If you show a flower at them, they will think in several dimensions before they act. &amp;quot;Flower might create a smell, the smell would bring attention of a few people there by reducing productivity and efficiency of his team. I should throw this flower out!&amp;quot;. Or, like &amp;quot; somebody would use this flower to impress a girl in team. They will get married. The girl would quit her work. I should immediately throw away the flower &amp;quot;. Manoj was a very good friend earlier. But the managerial mask made him a ninja clown in the team. Well, he still thinks he is Ninja but we could only see a clown in him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New mail from Manoj in outlook, &amp;#39; Meeting, rush! &amp;#39;. &amp;quot; I should teach this guy some emotion sometime &amp;quot;, I told to myself. I rushed to his room. He was in all smiles. I knew something was wrong. &amp;quot;Sachin, our client, the MD of AVP, pvt. Ltd., is very happy with our cooperation. He has invited one of our colleagues to his industry for a workshop. It&amp;#39;s an one month programme, which will help us build interpersonal skills, and strengthen our cooperation.&amp;quot;
All of a sudden, Manoj turned blue and i saw a chakra spinning behind his head. &amp;quot;Krishna??!!&amp;quot;
The &amp;#39;ever-interested&amp;#39; me showed my first disinterest in any offer at my company. &amp;quot;Sachin, I think you are the right person to represent us. You must go to Mumbai tomorrow.&amp;quot;
 I wanted to ask him, &amp;quot;so tell me what&amp;#39;s going on behind your head? Did I marry Jyotsna and she quits job after that?&amp;quot;. 
He continued, &amp;quot; Don&amp;#39;t worry Sachin! I would ask them to serve coffee regularly, since you have developed a taste for coffee recently &amp;quot;.
I rose my voice! &amp;quot; What&amp;#39;s your problem Manoj? What&amp;#39;s wrong in me drinking coffee? &amp;quot;
 &amp;quot; Well too much of caffeine is not good for health Sachin. Break is good for you. And for us.&amp;quot;
I hate it, when I live a life where people find things in me to spin sarcasms over. I like to be transparent because when nothing is fishy in life, I can face the sarcastic people on their bloody face!
What&amp;#39;s wrong if a guy and a girl goes out? They both have gravity by nature! Well well!! These fools are blind to nature, after all!!
&amp;quot;Well! I don&amp;#39;t like this behaviour in you Manoj. But ya, I will go!&amp;quot;
This is another instant in my life, I was searching for the baddest words in every language I know. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I came out, Jyotsna came to desk. 
&amp;quot;Yet another bad meeting you survived! And you need a coffee now. Am I right?&amp;quot;, in her tutty voice.
I lost all the thoughts. That was like how my dad, back from a long day at work, would react after seeing me when I was a kid. I reciprocated her emotion. We were drinking tea for a change. I kept rolling the tea bag on my cup. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are those few heavy moments in life where I feel,&amp;quot; can this moment vanish?&amp;quot;. I have to tell her that I am gonna go away for one full month. I will miss her! She will miss me too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-7.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-7.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 6</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wore red for a reason. I know he likes the color. Best part about him is, when he likes somebody wearing red, he openly acknowledges the person right in front of them. &amp;quot;I like the color. It looks good on you.&amp;quot;, I remember him telling Shweta. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was doing random things restlessly on his car, and he kept observing silently. New for me. New for him. As he kept driving long, I interrupted him, &amp;quot;Are we going to Pondicherry?&amp;quot; 
He starred at my eyes.
I asked him again, &amp;quot;did you already inform Manoj about half day leave?&amp;quot;
He had a shakedown. &amp;quot;No. I should go back.&amp;quot;
I continued, &amp;quot;well, if you keep driving without finding restaurant, we will reach Pondicherry&amp;quot;
He smiled. It was vibrant. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We found a restaurant. They had a table for two. We went there and sat opposite to each other. Waiter brought a candle to the table. God screws all our plan. But when he gives back, its more than worth the plan. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ordered lasagna for me and he ordered chicken steak for him. I tried not showing hesitation, but he did figure out that I don&amp;#39;t eat meat. He then converted his order into a barito. As i kept playing with plastic flower on the table, he broke the silence. &amp;quot;I am sorry. I screwed it up yesterday. I couldn&amp;#39;t fix the bike soon.&amp;quot; 
I was put in surprise. 
&amp;quot;It was Alan&amp;#39;s laziness first. And then his bike&amp;#39;s laziness. I couldn&amp;#39;t help it. And when I had come late, you weren&amp;#39;t there at our meeting spot. I dropped by at your home as well, looking for you. Did your mom tell you?&amp;quot;
I couldn&amp;#39;t resist. I laughed out loudly. So loudly that, the child in table next to us started crying. He apologised to everyone, sat back, held my hand tightly and asked me to be quite. Took a while for me. That face full of ignorance! I started liking him more. &amp;quot;Should I tell this poor guy, what happened on my side?&amp;quot; I asked myself. &amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t tell him.&amp;quot; Said my ego. I saved my story for future, for us to laugh at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started going out everyday. He would come to me with some reason to go out everyday. &amp;quot;I hate my manager&amp;quot;, &amp;quot; I hate my client &amp;quot;, &amp;quot;I am bored of sitting with computer &amp;quot;, &amp;quot;I am bored of machine coffee&amp;quot;, &amp;quot; you are beautiful today &amp;quot;, &amp;quot; long day. I think i need a break &amp;quot;, &amp;quot; I need a break &amp;quot;, &amp;quot; I just need a break &amp;quot;. My answer would be simply. &amp;quot; OK let&amp;#39;s go out for coffee &amp;quot;. Though people thought it was for coffee, zomato helped us roam out for good chat and dessert. &amp;#39;Pani poori day&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Pav bhajji day&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;kulfi day&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;cafe coffee day&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;brownie with ice cream day&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;caramel sundae&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;milk shake day&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;chaai day&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;green tea day&amp;#39;. It&amp;#39;s not all. We started taking more breaks during work too. The many many coffee mugs people gifted me for all these days started helping us. Each break, we would go to different wings in our building with different coffee mugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our relationship started to build over coffee. Life is becoming so beautiful all of a sudden.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-6.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-6.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 5</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I missed my alarm. As usual! But Thiru didn&amp;#39;t! Thiru won&amp;#39;t. &amp;quot;Ende Bhaagyam!!&amp;quot; I used to say to myself, wherever I wonder Thiru is my Room-mate. And he is best in waking me from sleep,. &amp;quot;Well, he is second best, he is only after my mom.&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s Monday!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had something close to fear of death, which drove me crazy. My body temperature was raising and falling like all 4 seasons are happening in me every half hour. But I wanted to meet her. For the first time in life, I was happy to run towards my fear. What a mixed feeling it is! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, everytime i am disappointed, I show it on my car. Yesterday, I had kicked him right on his bonnet. I was afraid if he would refuse to start. I have an emotional connection with my car. I went to him, keyed him on. Before trying on starter, I went like &amp;quot;Lakshmi! Start aaidu ma&amp;quot;. In memory of thalaivar from movie padikkaathavan. My Lakshmi did start on first attempt. In memory of bay of Bengal, Chennai people are working on a new variety of traffic each day. You cannot move, until you learn to swim. But it took only half the usual time to reach office. &amp;quot; When I am hoping for some good to happen in life, you screw my bike and my day. But when I am hoping for a deadly encounter, you can even dilute Chennai traffic in peak hour. God! You are marvellous!!&amp;quot;, I looked up with my nerves carrying the blood full of sarcasm. I walked towards my cubicle. &amp;quot;She hasn&amp;#39;t come yet!!&amp;quot;. I used to have a sigh of relief of living an extra day, whenever my history teacher in school used to postpone the distribution of exam papers. That feeling was back in life. &amp;quot;A few more minutes before you die&amp;quot;, I told to myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was 9am. My reminder in outlook popped up with message &amp;quot; Book tatkal for mom and dad&amp;quot;. Mata IRCTC ! It&amp;#39;s time to fight for her darshan!!! To book a tatkal ticket in India, you have to follow three rules. 1. Patience, and falling down head over heals to Mata IRCTC 2. Patience, even after you fail 3. Patience, like you are about to attain motksha. I go to the corner of my campus with my tab, the only place where my data connection will show some mercy.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thiru is our godfather, he is the only person from our friends circle who can understand every bit about Mata. He knows shortcuts so that he can confirm his birth, when half of us would fail to get even a waiting list ticket. When we all assemble 10 minutes early, he comes in front of computer at 9:30 to book a single ticket. &amp;quot;That 20 minutes gap between him and us, i call it dedication and discipline&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was about to get 10am. When you are logged in inside irctc, she didn&amp;#39;t like you disturbing her often, nor not disturbing her. So you should master the number of times you are gonna disturb her. More than that, you need to master yourself to wait for her reactions. It was 10:00:00am. I was excited. I clicked &amp;quot; load trains &amp;quot;. She kept rolling her eyes, Mata is known for that. After 5 minutes, I lost my patience. I clicked &amp;quot; load trains &amp;quot; one more time. She through me out! Right away! &amp;#39;You have either pressed back button or forward button or both. To re-login, please click here&amp;#39;. What is that in the whole world!! These are the only possible options! Even Super Mario gives you an opportunity to start from any level where mario dies, but not irctc! Mata asks you to re-login freshly again!! Incoming mail, it was Thiru. &amp;quot;Hey da! Booking confirmed. PFA&amp;quot;. Thiru, is simply our godfather!!! He owes a bit higher respect to that of father, from all of us! One more mail. It was my manager this time. &amp;quot; Client meeting. Rush &amp;quot;, he writes mail like sms. You can&amp;#39;t figure out his mood. So, in all chances, you have to rush to his room. I did rush. And then the meeting went on for half day. It was one of many many meetings I survived, which could have been better conveyed with a single mail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was getting back, hunger was beginning to eat me. And then, I saw Jyotsna. &amp;quot; Well here it is! Go face her. You can! Tell her the truth. It&amp;#39;s going to be alright! &amp;quot; That&amp;#39;s simply how I face things in life.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was smiling. It was like a Raja sir song. Her eyes were so bright and complimenting. It was like the counter pointing bass line Raja sir uses. She was wearing a red saree. It was flying in air like Raja sir&amp;#39;s strings composition. &amp;quot;Raja Sir, kolreengale!!!&amp;quot; I tapped over my chest. I lost the fear totally! 
&amp;quot;You are so beautiful!&amp;quot;, I said. She looked at me with surprise. I felt like Vaali Sir wrote all those songs for me. There was an external silence with internal storm. I wanted to keep the silence. It was beautiful! Both of us kept the silence for a while. Then I broke it as usual. 
&amp;quot;I am hungry&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;quot;Ok, let&amp;#39;s go out for lunch&amp;quot;, she said.
I didn&amp;#39;t want to talk one bit more. Wherever gives me a chance to make up, I do it strongly. 
&amp;quot;Shall I call people to join us?&amp;quot;, that would have been the stupidest of the questions I would ask her. She remained silent. 
&amp;quot;Okay, you wait here. I will get keys from Alan&amp;quot;.
&amp;quot; Don&amp;#39;t you have your car?? &amp;quot; She whispered. 
&amp;quot;Well, yes. Yes! We shall go. Let&amp;#39;s go. Please come.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Man! This is simply awesome. This feeling. This silence. I feel the butterflies. Alan calls it &amp;quot;Butterfly effect: a butterfly&amp;#39;s effect&amp;quot;. There was nervousness outside. But my inner self was at peace, total peace! I loved these kind of mixed emotions. I felt like each word I drop here would spoil the scene like drops of paint over clear water. I remained silent. She sat on my car in the front, adjusted ac and tuned FM. She was as if she was owning my car. I loved that freedom in her when she was with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday, I love you! For probably first time in life!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-5.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-5.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 4</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think I am unlucky. He is a gentleman. He had a respect over me. I think I lost it completely today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relatives play an important role in spoiling all our plans. Right from our childhood. &amp;quot;Relatives, please change your name as spoilers&amp;quot;. My father wanted to buy a bullet. He was crazy about royal Enfield, he still is. If you ask him to choose between a bullet and Rolls Royce he would go for bullet. &amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s just the kingmanship&amp;quot;, he keeps saying. He used to tell me stories about his 20s. He was saving money to buy a bullet. He waited for 3-4 years to save enough money to buy one bullet. He apparently made an order too. That was simply the time when his uncle visited home with my mom&amp;#39;s horoscope. You know what the fate is, he hasn&amp;#39;t got his bullet yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was in my 9th grade, my father decided to put me in an international school in ooty. I was thoroughly excited. In summer break after 8th grade, my father had taken me to ooty. The school was excellent. The weather was too good. The toy train track was right next to our school campus. They had student body theatre club. Sound of train, misty weather, theatre club, those were just the three things I was longing for years! And then, just a couple of weeks before I start my schooling in ooty, mala Aunty had come home. She isn&amp;#39;t my mom&amp;#39;s sister, she is my life spoiler. Have you read the book by Varun Agarwal? She is simply the Anu Aunty. In two hours, she proved to my parents that my later school in Chennai was 10 times better than my dream school in ooty. She had even brought her kid and made him perform aasanaas in front of my whole family, to impress them with yoga they teach in my later school. &amp;quot;I say you today, lady with big red torch light on forehead, I am counting on your spoilers and i will give you back every single one in future&amp;quot; I used to say to myself, everytime she is home. But the counter is overflowing. And I am helplessly and hopelessly waiting for day to give her back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet again, she is the one who spoiled it totally today. Friends!! If any of your relatives are doing MLM business, please be double aware of them. I was getting ready. Sachin was everywhere in my mind. And that&amp;#39;s when she arrived home, yet again in 11th hour, yet again with spoiler bombs!! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wherever she is home, I can know that she is home much before I could see her. As soon as she enters our home, the place will be set to silence, the silence you could probably find only at places like Antarctica centre or top of Himalayas. A strange loud deafening noise will break the silence. &amp;quot;Haaaiiii puppyyyy&amp;quot;. She calls my mom puppy. Some day my father would possibly run and jump out of compound wall, due to the trauma of her frightening voice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She had brought white &amp;quot; Dappaas&amp;quot; of various sizes. &amp;quot;Puppy, look at the new entrepreneur!!&amp;quot;. My father looked at her back with expression of expecting someone. Only both of us know that, everytime he deliberately does that! &amp;quot; ohh Maheshh! I am the new entrepreneur &amp;quot;. My heart was broken into as many pieces as the number of &amp;quot; dabbaas&amp;quot; she had brought. I knew she is going to start with some marketing demonstration. If I go to somebody&amp;#39;s home, I wouldn&amp;#39;t start by boasting. &amp;#39;how are you&amp;#39; would be my first words. Mala Aunty always starts with boasting. &amp;quot;My day is screwed! Totally!&amp;quot; My pulse rate raised! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you guys watch cricket? I watch test matches with my dad! He loves watching it with me. Her entrance was like India bowled out completely with the last wicket tail ender pair batting on 5th day of an away test match! Only rain could save the match! &amp;quot;God save me!&amp;quot; I whispered. She was in the middle of her boasting about the MLM business she is been doing recently. My father wanted to find a way to relieve me.
&amp;quot;Hey saleslady!&amp;quot;, my father went on calling Mala Aunty in his tonic voice.
&amp;quot;How rude Mahesh!&amp;quot;, my mom interfered. 
&amp;quot; Oh then how should I call you ?&amp;quot;
Mala Aunty spoke, &amp;quot;call me business girl Mahesh&amp;quot;. 
&amp;quot; If you are a girl, then what is Jyotsna?&amp;quot; My dad read my mind.
&amp;quot;Aww she is still &amp;#39;namma kozhantha&amp;#39; (our very own kid) na&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Alright business girl, our kid should go out now&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Why??&amp;quot; She screamed.
The one thing I hate about my father was that, he doesn&amp;#39;t know to lie! &amp;quot;Today is her birthday and she is going out with friends&amp;quot;, he answered her like the 11th man opened up all three sticks to the pace bowler. 
&amp;quot;Oh my God... Kozhantha... It&amp;#39;s your birthday today?? How can you leave  athai and go out? I will cook some sweet for you. You must stay.&amp;quot; Mala Aunty and my mom on one side. Me and my father on other side. Mom wins over father and so, we lost the last wicket too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time was already 3, when they went to the kitchen. I could have still escaped. But once when I had done like that early, mum did a big drama of not eating food. &amp;quot;He is punctual. He must have arrived by now.&amp;quot;  She cooked some weird pale pinky dish which she called herself a apple cake. They made me cut it. My father took photographs. It was around 5. My faces were like, how I used to hold my piss during long afternoon classes after lunch break during my 6th grade. She continued to brain wash my mom and dad with her MLM. My father interrupted, &amp;quot;Priya, at least now we should let her go.&amp;quot; My mom nodded her head up and down. &amp;quot;I love you pa&amp;quot;, I kissed him and ran out of the place. &amp;quot; Jyo...&amp;quot; screamed the Mala Aunty. &amp;quot;I will come next Sunday and give you one separate session. You should join us. You know, you can earn when you are studying only.&amp;quot; 
and my father interrupted, &amp;quot;she is done with her studies and she is working now&amp;quot; . 
&amp;quot;Oh aamaa la... Ok go...&amp;quot;
I was Indian of year 1947.
&amp;quot;Jyooo...&amp;quot; She again screamed. 
&amp;quot;Huh Aunty&amp;quot; like a sudden heavy vehicle break on highway.
&amp;quot;You should not go out with guys, OK?&amp;quot; She is a witch. None other than a witch.
&amp;quot;Okay Aunty&amp;quot; this time I planned to shut my ear drums off and run like deer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fifth Street was empty. So much empty as my heart was. &amp;quot;I can&amp;#39;t handle this, God why did you do this to me???&amp;quot; Nervousness lowered down my blood pressure. Vision darkened. &amp;quot;He must have waited for long. I made the gentleman wait. I hate myself.&amp;quot;  There was only one person on earth I would run to at scenarios like this. My dad. I wanted to come back home. But I was not interested to meet the witch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went to my friend&amp;#39;s place. We went to cafe near by and celebrated my birthday over a slice of black forest. I hated the day. The birthdays should begin well for the year to be well throughout. But this birthday was sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had come back home late in the night. &amp;quot;Jyoo, your colleague by the name Sachin had come home.&amp;quot;, my mom said. I was freezed to silence. You know, that&amp;#39;s most wounding moment. He had come, he had waited in fifth Street patiently. He had come home later looking for me. I felt like a Bitch. &amp;quot; No Sachin, I am not a Bitch &amp;quot; i sounded to myself. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mondays are generally haunting. But there was one person named Sachin who used to turn them around. Now the reason behind is Sachin himself. I feel like a Bitch. How am I gonna face him tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-4.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-4.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 3</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I blew it up. How am I gonna face her tomorrow? At least I must have taken my car. I mean, what is about this bike thing? Why are girls so obsessed with bikes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alan totally twisted the day. I thought he was one of the very few trustworthy friends. But he is indeed trustworthy. I missed a point. My friends!! If you ever ask for a favour from somebody, ask from the one who isn&amp;#39;t lazy. Even if he isn&amp;#39;t trustworthy, that&amp;#39;s OK. Because laziness is mother of all evil. Laziness can anyday win over trustworthiness. And screw up your day completely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was 2:30pm already. I lost hopes on him and i rushed to his place, only to find him on his couch, sleeping peacefully. I was thinking of any ridiculous way to wake him. The TV was on, but was on mute. I took the remote and immediately increased the volume to maximum. He fell off the bed and wiped his eyes several times. Before he could recognise me, he started his hilarious reasons. &amp;quot;machaan, I had kept alarm. But the mobile got switched off without power.&amp;quot; Every now and then people get me on nerves, but only on a few occasions, they get to see the reddish nerves popping out of my eyes. It was one of those occasions. He continued, &amp;quot;machaan, I anticipated this and I had informed my mom to remind me as well.&amp;quot; I spoke, &amp;quot;where is your mom?&amp;quot; She entered the house carrying a bag full of groceries, &amp;quot;hey Sachin, when did you come? He didn&amp;#39;t tell me that you would come.&amp;quot; I was burning him with my eyes. His mom continued, &amp;quot;nevertheless, please come and have lunch. I have made chicken. This guy is sleeping the whole day. You don&amp;#39;t wait for him&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before Alan was ashes, he took me to his parking shed. Gorgeous classic 350 was standing on its side stand. Like a boss! His wrangler helmet went so well with my aviator. I tried sitting on it and i was feeling Swag. When i drove out of his house it was 3:10pm. &amp;quot;She must be already in 5th street waiting for me near the bakery.&amp;quot; My thoughts tightened me up. I was losing control. I made her wait for me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These were the very few occasions I had ever felt I am being too idealistic. &amp;quot;I think I should get a phone.&amp;quot; I was already late. I thought I should pass on a message to her saying I am late. &amp;quot;What&amp;#39;s wrong with this city? Where are those beautiful telephone booths with which Ajith and Devayani romanced in their times??&amp;quot; The road was empty enough for me to touch 80s. &amp;quot;I thank you God!! For emptying this road&amp;quot; And then, something happened. The bike was slowing down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friends!! If you would ever borrow a bike from a friend on emergencies, borrow a familiar one. &amp;quot;What the hell is wrong with you? Why did you stop, bloody?&amp;quot; I kept kicking the starter pedal , &amp;quot;awww common, why aren&amp;#39;t you starting now??&amp;quot;. The roads are empty. &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t thank you God! For emptying the road!!&amp;quot; I then made a choice to push and roll the classic 350 and walk a bit until my eyes spots any ray of hope. &amp;quot;I hate you God!!&amp;quot; Like God was listening to me over a wireless, he responded so fast! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a mechanic shop. When the mechanic guy came out, I spotted a glow of light in the back of his head. &amp;quot;Now how do I explain him what went wrong in this bloody bike? I frankly have no idea&amp;quot;. I was collecting words and breaking my voice. 
&amp;quot; No problem Sir. Naan paathukuren &amp;quot; he was God. He was simply God. He kicked the pedal several times too, &amp;quot;well, then I did it correctly. The problem is actually with bike &amp;quot; I has a sigh of relief. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had a mobile phone. This time, i planned to ask God his mobile phone. &amp;quot;Can I borrow your phone Need to make an important call!&amp;quot; He treated me like his boss. He is God after all. When I opened my phone book, her number was written in legible and bold letter. God peeped into my phone book and read the name. He asked me, &amp;quot;Yaar Sir? Unga figuraa?&amp;quot; He is not God! He is definitely not god. There was a thirst in his eyes when he asked like that. I gave him his mobile without the call. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was 4:30 when the bike was ready. I know the day is gone. I know I blew it up. But I wanted to drive to the fifth street anyway. I expected, she might be waiting inspite of the time delays. That&amp;#39;s what happens in all Tamil films. When I reached our meeting spot, she wasn&amp;#39;t there. &amp;quot;Tamil film directors!! You never spin a story close to reality&amp;quot;. A part of my mind told me to go to her home. Another part told me not to go. In these 50-50 scenarios, our gravity is naturally towards the 50 which will spoil the scene. I went to her home with the last hopes. There were a lot of relatives at her place. Her mom told she had gone out. &amp;quot;I burn Alan after I am ashes myself tomorrow!&amp;quot;. Her mom was kind, she noted my name. She might tell her that I at least came late. That might reduce the after effects tomorrow. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one of those few Sundays I hated! And tomorrow is one of those deadly Mondays. This time, it&amp;#39;s not manager, client, but her.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-3.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-3.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I have called him to take me out. I have never been out with any guy alone. This is all new for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said he has a car. I am so afraid about bikes. I must have let him come in his car. &amp;quot;Why did I ask for a bike ride then? &amp;quot; because he likes drama in life. I am sure he will borrow one from his friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is so transparent. He opens up so easily. I struggle to speak. I fear embarrassments. I fear people. But he is simply funny. He doesn&amp;#39;t give a shit about people&amp;#39;s opinions and ideas. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work together. He is smart and extremely calm at workplace. He is the kind of guy, every new girl in the team would like to get mentored under. He often tries to be nice to people. But there are smartasses in team who put him into embarrassment. What do you do when somebody embarrass you so much? And make others laugh at you? I will kill the guy 10 times in my mind with minimum 5 different weapons. He simply talks about his ignorance which put him into embarrassment, he talks about it so many times that he can come over it. He also talks in a way that multiplies people&amp;#39;s laughter and smile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His voice has got a warmth. I love to listen to him speak. We hardly get time to talk though. But everytime he was around, he is the one who speaks more. I let him speak more. There are occasions he would ask me questions, I give him one line answer. I would think &amp;quot;what is so interesting about me to tell him&amp;quot;. He doesn&amp;#39;t own a mobile phone. People make fun of him. They say, he is from a different time frame, a much older time Frame. Sometimes some people enquire about old people who are dead, &amp;quot; Hi machaa, how are you? How&amp;#39;s Gandhi, Nehru? Will India get independence this year? &amp;quot;. But I respected that part of him, he has some ideas about life and he lives by them under any circumstance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He once called me out. Many people have approached me till date. He was decent. He asked for coffee together. I played a Bitch. I told I drink only beer. I very well know that would have hurt him. But I also know he is strong enough to take it. I was fearing. I was fearing that I would fall for him. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I have called Sachin for a date. It took sometime for me to come over my fear. Or may be that I don&amp;#39;t fear anymore because I have already fallen for him. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today is my birthday. He doesn&amp;#39;t know about that. It would be a surprise, he love surprises. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I shouldn&amp;#39;t blow it up. I have to speak more. Speak my heart out, like he does always. Make him realise he is important. And then, things will fall into place. I believe in gravity. I believe in love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today is the day my friends. Today is the day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-2.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 12</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;He dropped me at central. It&amp;#39;s a long journey. &amp;quot;Sothappidaadha chellame&amp;quot;, he said with puppy face. I gave him a hug and said &amp;quot; same to you chellame!&amp;quot;. Train started to move. I was getting nervous. Sachin&amp;#39;s parents are difficult ones. They were always strict at him. More than how my parents accept him, his parents should accept me. That&amp;#39;s how it works here in south India. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had shopped the whole day on Saturday. I had bought sarees for Aunty and party wear shirt, dhoties for uncle. Uncle likes the ghee mysoorpa from Krishna. I had bought a couple of boxes of it. I was carrying the only half saree I had, to wear at their place. Aunty loves half saree. I know about my father. He respects my decisions in life. His meeting with Sachin will be a sort of formality thing. I was worrying too much about mine. The sunshine woke me up from train window. I saw gaint windmills on both side of the train. It was a beautiful scene. I wished he was with me. Freshened up. Took a coffee. And was waiting for my station. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagerkoil :) such a beautiful city. Fresh morning. I followed Sachin&amp;#39;s instructions. His town is a little bit away from city. I took a town bus. And got down at &amp;#39;paala karai&amp;#39; stop. There was a huge banyan tree like he had mentioned. I walked straight towards it and crossed the tree on its left. Then proceeded in the mud road under canopy of trees on both side of road. Then finally i found the lake. There was auto drivers. As I was getting closer, they started welcoming me. Such a good smile and warm look that you can never find in any auto driver back in my city. I was giving him the address. He said he knew where to drop. It was a small but lovely village. It had shades of Kerala. Weather was optimum. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We reached Sachin&amp;#39;s house. It was a small house with Mangalore tiles. I paid auto driver. He didn&amp;#39;t take the money from me and told me that uncle paid him in morning, on his way to church. As I was stepping inside his house, I was hearing kids singing. The music was coming from right corner of the house. I slowly walked towards it. It was Aunty singing along with bunch of kids. They were singing the carnatic Raag &amp;#39;Gambeera Naattai&amp;quot;. I stood there at doorstep with my eyes closed and embraced the music. It was a lovely and peaceful sound. It was 25 minutes straight. Then there was a silence. The kids were all starring at me. Aunty asked kids to continue singing and came out of the room. They continued with &amp;#39;kaanada&amp;#39;. She welcomed me with a kind of smile. It was the most purest face I have ever seen in life. She touched my head with her palm, and enquired how the train journey was. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She took me to a room. It was Sachin&amp;#39;s room. It had a lot of his childhood stuff, photos, cups he had won. She made me comfortable. I went for bath. As I was getting back, I could hear uncle&amp;#39;s voice. Kids kept singing. I came out after dressing up. Aunty looked at me and stood still for a moment. I smiled at her. Uncle came by her and they both smiled at me. Half saree worked. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uncle was 5 times as talkative as Sachin. He told all stories about his church choir. He was a baryton singer. No wonder why Sachin&amp;#39;s voice is so warm. Then I met one interesting girl. &amp;#39;Pammi&amp;#39;. She was simply the village kid. She was the daughter of their maid. Aunty introduced her and said, &amp;quot;Kannaa, you can have breakfast and then Pammi would take you out. You can go to the farms here. Village sight seeing. Your cities won&amp;#39;t have such good places. She will then bring you back for lunch.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pammi was 10 times as talkative as Sachin. But she had sweet voice. We met so many people on our way. She introduced everyone to me. They all had a special respect for Uncle. The whole village was like a family. Everybody knew each other very well. Unlike the high and wide apartments in cities where we don&amp;#39;t know our neighbours well. Farms, well, nature. The day was turning out to be magical. There was a swing tied up in one of those trees. I became a kid and began to play. Pammi pushed me from behind. Her cristal laughs were adding the flavour to my joy. I was at my peak of energy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We then returned back. She came to me and with her loud tone, told me &amp;quot;Akka neenga romba azhagaa irukkeenga&amp;quot; (you look very beautiful). People are so open there. Sachin is simply a part of that village. I couldn&amp;#39;t resist myself from kissing her. When I returned home, the kids were all leaving. One kid asked Aunty, &amp;quot;Intha Akka yaaru?&amp;quot; (Who is this?). Aunty told them, &amp;quot;She is your Athai. She is going to marry Sachin Mama&amp;quot;. 
Sometimes language is too limited to express our emotions. Lovely lovely moment it was. I stood there speechless. The kids all shouted in love, &amp;quot; Hai Athaiiii&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;#39;t speak a word. I was trying to control my tears. They served lunch. It wasn&amp;#39;t food. It was simply the solidified form of love. I had hickups in between. Uncle ran to bring water while aunty tried to rub at my back. They were struggling to get rid of Hickups I had. Love. Simply love. Everything was Ultaa! Unexpectedly beautiful! Like a rain in mid of hot month of April. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I took a nap. The last time I slept so peacefully was probably when I was a kid. Aunty woke me up again in evening. Asked me to get ready for my train. I gave them sarees and shirts and all the gifts I had bought for them. They were very happy. Hyper excited. I gave one box of sweets to Pammi. It was time to leave. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before leaving I fell over their feet to get their blessing. When I stood up again, I saw aunty crying. I couldn&amp;#39;t control my tears anymore. &amp;quot;I can&amp;#39;t believe uncle&amp;quot;, I whispered. &amp;quot;Did Sachin threaten you too much about us? We showed strictness in bringing him up, because he should be truthful and honest to people. But we love him and trust him. We knew that you would be a nice girl. We simply knew. Because it was his choice.&amp;quot;, he said. &amp;quot; do visit us often. Bring him next time when you come. &amp;quot; aunty continued. 
&amp;quot;I promise aunty!&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Auto was waiting for me. Uncle helped me put my bag in auto. He paid the driver and asked him to drop me directly in junction. Then he came to me and spoke a few final words, &amp;quot; we are Christians. But we don&amp;#39;t mind your culture. You can see, aunty loves carnatic music. She is a trained singer and she teaches class. We only don&amp;#39;t have a krishna photo at our place. If there are any troubles at your side because of this fact, tell me. I would try to speak with your family. Because, you guys must live long together. That&amp;#39;s our wish. &amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was speechless. I wanted to win their heart. But I got defeated by their overwhelming love. On the way to junction, auto driver spoke few words. He said, uncle and aunty are feeling a bit lonely since Sachin visits them rarely these days. I made him a promise that I would bring Sachin soon again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I feel I don&amp;#39;t deserve such good moments in life. It is one of those times. Sachin was waiting in central to receive me with a curious face. I simply hugged him. Hug lasted for nearly 5 minutes. I cried. He was in smile. He understood the tears were out of happiness. I began to speak.
&amp;quot;You know why everything is falling into place?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Because you are a lovely girl and you deserve it&amp;quot; he said. 
&amp;quot;No. It&amp;#39;s not for us. But for those lovely people who gave birth to us. They deserve this story of love in their life.&amp;quot; 
We had smile. It was full. I couldn&amp;#39;t believe any moment which happened in past few days of life. Right from the day I met Sachin, to this day. Things happened as beautiful as metaphorical poems. I was wondering, when love is this much beautiful, why would even people write songs on break ups and hatred. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were on his car. Getting back to my place. The second most beautiful Monday of my life. There was just silence. As if a silence after a storm. As we were entering our house, there were lot of horoscopes lying on the table in middle of hall. 
I got a shock out of trauma. Sachin was holding my hand tightly and asked me, &amp;quot;What happened Jyo?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Mala aunty!!!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;story ends&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-12.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-12.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sachin Jyotsna, a love story - scene 11</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a girl friend during my graduation days. Things were so beautiful between us, until the day we both confessed the love to each other. The later part of that love story had the following words: expectations, desperation, longing, depression, insanity, emotional black mailing, and lastly &amp;quot;break up&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Jyotsna and I were in love, we both managed our days without explicit confessions. But people around us were getting more curious and restless. That was putting us into trouble and embarrassments most times. We had added-up complications in our story like, she was a Hindu brahmin, I was a Christian. And beyond all this, I wanted to get rid of the mobile phone in my life. Hence one fine day we came up with a plan. &amp;quot; Sachin, you should come to my house and talk to my father about us. I will go to your home and talk to your parents&amp;quot;, she said. That was sounding great. We both knew the likes and dislikes of our parents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was getting a call from Roshan, &amp;quot;machaa, I am coming to Chennai this Sunday&amp;quot; 
&amp;quot;Great da! Wow! What&amp;#39;s up?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;We are performing at the meridian.&amp;quot; 
Something struck me hard. Mahesh loves Jazz!!!! 
&amp;quot;You are the best Roshan! I love you I love you I love you.&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Hahaa what happened machaa&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Can you get me a couple of tickets?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Of course machaa! I am inviting you!!&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Super! I will call you right back&amp;quot;
I disconnected Roshan and dialled Alan. &amp;quot;Hi machaa, what&amp;#39;s up?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Dei, can I borrow your bullet for a day? This Sunday?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Dei, athukkulla innoru figure ah? What happened to Jyotsna?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;If I you are next to me right now, you will shed blood on your nose&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Well, alright! I was joking machaan. You can take it.&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Thanks a lot da! Can I also have it on Saturday?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Well, sure but why?&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;To have a service done in prior. &amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well that&amp;#39;s everything falling into place. I then dialled up Jyotsna to check whether Mahesh is free on Sunday. He was free. She planned her tickets on Saturday night to go to my home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had prepared scripts on what to speak, what not to speak. Father of each girl would look for somebody who can look after their girl like them! When I mean like them, its the most difficult thing on earth! Like how they carried her over their shoulders and ran to make her win each time, be it a race or be it life. Mahesh would expect me to be that guy. I wanted to convince that I can take care of Jyotsna better than him. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday arrived. I had gone to their home in afternoon. Mahesh was watching highlights of a old English test match, in which Dravid would carry his bat after a lone man century. Aunty showed a bit of hesitation at my arrival. Mahesh welcomed me with a smile and a tight hand shake. 
&amp;quot;Please come in Sachin.&amp;quot;
Then he went into the kitchen, after a long murmuring chat with Jyotsna&amp;#39;s mom, he came back and said &amp;quot;give me 10 minutes, I will be back after a shower.&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Sure take your time uncle.&amp;quot; 
He then threw the TV remote to me, &amp;quot;please feel free to change channel. Feel like your home, son&amp;quot; he said. 
I was least interested in TV. I then scanned the TV room and all the photographs on wall. It was full of Jyotsna. Her every single moment in life was freezed into photo frame. Birthdays, dance arangetram, sports wins, competition wins, her friends circle, her childhood, her portraits, beach moments, family portraits. &amp;quot;I can never become Mahesh&amp;quot;, I told to myself. 
When he said 10minutes, he was out in 8 minutes and a few seconds. &amp;quot;I can never become Mahesh&amp;quot;, I repeated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was totally delighted to see the classic 350. I then gave him the keys and asked him to drive. He was double delighted. We drove, drove and drove long. Initially he was a bit nasty. Then he became stable in driving. He drove me to Pondicherry. We went to beach. Sat on those rocks. Starred at the sea for long time. Didn&amp;#39;t speak a word. Then drove to ashram there. He looked for some books. Bought a couple. Then we started back. While coming back, we took turns in driving. We stopped everywhere for a tea or tender coconut. We talked politics, philosophies, cricket. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we were reaching Chennai, I drove him to Meridian. He asked me, &amp;quot; Why to meridian? Let&amp;#39;s go home for dinner. I will ask Priya to prepare something&amp;quot;. 
&amp;quot;Surprise uncle! Ask Aunty not to prepare anything. You are going to enjoy the evening&amp;quot;
When we entered meridian, he made a call. The call took a while. I was afraid that her mom isn&amp;#39;t happy about me. As soon as we entered the concert hall, Mahesh showed his excitement in a loud voice, &amp;quot;Woooow! You made my day, Son!&amp;quot;. They had several round tables with seats around. Roshan had booked a couple of seats for us, very near to the stage. They were serving drinks. Mahesh was hyper excited. He socialised with table mates so easily. They went on for a toast, after each track. He enjoyed every bit of it. He was literally living his day. A 50 year old man could drive all the way back and forth to Pondicherry in classic 350 in a single day and he could party the same night. He had so much energy! More than everything, he was doing every possible thing as if he will have no regrets at all. &amp;quot;I think Jyotsna likes me because I am a small reflection of Mahesh&amp;quot; I told to myself. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roshan took the mike and said, &amp;quot;this is our last song. We are dedicating this one for our special friend, Mahesh&amp;quot;. It was a couple of ARR&amp;#39;s songs in Jazz style, Mahesh is a big fan of ARR, especially his early music in 90s. It was all planned. Mahesh was put in tears. He came to me and hugged me tight. &amp;quot; I think I made it&amp;quot;, I told to myself. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We came out. It was 12 midnight. Mahesh asked me for bike key. He could barely stand. He was high. I asked him to sit at the back. I dropped him home. He thanked me for the day. He was drunk. I was in two minds. &amp;#39;Is this the better time to ask him, if I can marry his daughter&amp;#39;, my mind was fighting. The whole day I couldn&amp;#39;t speak a single word about his daughter. &amp;quot;Jyotsna is gonna kill me&amp;quot;, I told myself. He then came back. &amp;quot; Sachin, I need to book a tatkal ticket tomorrow. Heard from Jyo that you are good at it. Can you come home in morning? &amp;quot;. The first request from my father in law. &amp;quot; sure uncle! &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thiru is out of station. But I was confident. I reached back Jyotsna&amp;#39;s house at 9 next day. Mahesh was up. We sat with computer at 9:30. I felt like student taking his test without his master for first time. I did everything right. Logged in at 9:50. Waited till 10. Browsed for trains. Made clicks with patience. Everything was going fine, till payment page. Then Mata IRCTC stopped to respond. I waited, waited and waited. Then she said, &amp;quot;Sorry, you have clicked refresh or back or you have left the page idle for longtime. You need to re-login&amp;quot;. I felt like throwing the monitor out of the window. &amp;quot; those were the bloody three things possible things anybody on earth could do&amp;quot;, I yelled at computer. Aunty peeped in. &amp;quot;Everything is OK?&amp;quot;. &amp;quot; ya Aunty! &amp;quot; already she hates me. On top of it, this! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did re-login. It was waiting list 27 already! I lost the test! My first test! Frustrations were building up. Mahesh was taking a shower. &amp;quot;How am I going to face him? How am I going to face Jyotsna?&amp;quot;. Then Mahesh came into the room. When I was about to apologise, he said, &amp;quot; Thanks man! Incredible! You have booked a 3rd AC ticket! Impossible stuff &amp;quot;, looking at his mobile. THIRUUUU :) I had texted the details to my master anyways as a back up. I wasn&amp;#39;t sure, whether he was in a place to access Internet. Thiru is my God father! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was about to leave and I heard Aunty murmuring something to uncle. I peeped into the kitchen to say a bye. She was saying, &amp;quot; did you confirm with him that the wedding should be in Brahmin style? &amp;quot;. 
Friends!! This is the moment of my life!!!!! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They then became conscious of my presence. There was silence. I said bye to them. Then Mahesh walked along with me to send me off. He put his hand over my shoulders and said, &amp;quot; a few months back, my daughter was unhappy. She had something going on in her mind. Myself and Priya, we never question her personal conflicts. She share it when it&amp;#39;s necessary for her. That&amp;#39;s how we have brought her up. That was a well one week. She refused to share anything at all. We both tried our best to cheer her. We failed at doing it for first ever time in our life. Then one fine day she became happy all of a sudden. After that, till today I see my daughter with all smiles!&amp;quot;
He paused for a while. I was getting nervous! 
&amp;quot;I came to know that, he had gone out that day to meet a gentleman! Since then, I was waiting for this one day you would come to me and have a word!&amp;quot;
I was speechless! He looked at my face. Started smiling! 
&amp;quot;Will you marry my daughter? Because I believe she will be happy living a life with you&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;#39;t cry! I felt proud. Earning a girl&amp;#39;s love is hard. Earning her father&amp;#39;s respect is harder. I hugged him tight. Though in corner of my mind, I was still afraid that my parents would refuse a Hindu way of wedding. Mahesh continued, &amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t worry about Priya! You guys plan your wedding. I can convince my wife to come to church. My daughter&amp;#39;s happiness is important to me than my social and cultural status.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friends. I am at extreme emotions now. Waiting at the station to receive Jyotsna. Its clear on my side. Her side story would decide the result. My parents are the tough ones. Fingers crossed!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-11.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://karthiksblog.github.io//stories/2015/10/20/sachin-jyotsna-a-love-story-scene-11.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
